{
  "questions": {
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Meen habeeb baba?",
            "anwsers": ["Ana", "Yazeed", "Hamo", "Mohamed Mounir"],
            "right_answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "El sa7 el da7 emboo, edy el wad le ....",
            "anwsers": ["Abooh", "Akhooh", "Embooh", "Shame on you!"],
            "right_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Adel Shakal's crush?",
            "anwsers": ["Mona Zaki", "Dina", "Sama Elmasry", "Safinaz"],
            "right_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "When did Wasla hired Peter?",
            "anwsers": ["June 2018", "Nov 2018", "Jan 2019", "Mar 2005"],
            "right_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Edy edelo 3abelo fe shkara, ana 3amel demagh ....",
            "anwsers": ["Gabara", "Nawara", "Dawara", "Nadara"],
            "right_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Edy edelo 3abel fel kees, ana 3amel demagh ....",
            "anwsers": ["Sosees", "Autobees", "El ra2ees", "Tahyees"],
            "right_answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Which national team has won the AFCON 2019?",
            "anwsers": ["Egypt", "Egypt", "Egypt", "Egypt"],
            "right_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who's the current Egyptian Prisednet?",
            "anwsers": ["Elsisi", "Mo Salah", "Mubarak", "Abdel Nasser"],
            "right_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Ibrahim El Abyad's partner in crime?",
            "anwsers": ["Shokry", "Zohdy", "3ashry", "Fekry"],
            "right_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Hakona ....",
            "anwsers": ["Matata", "Batata", "Zatata", "Galata"],
            "right_answer": 1
        }
    ],
    "scores": {
        "correct": 10,
        "pass": 5,
        "wrong": 0
    }
  },
  "scores": []
}
